They're about to exit the tunnel!
No! Not good! Darby's ahead!
And by a full car length!
Our speed is about to be doubled!
It looks like I win!
No!
The fact of the matter is, I still
have more speed than you, Darby!
You're in for it now!
No!
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
Cocculeen had enough power
to spin his car around
and knock Darby's car
clear off the racetrack!
He used his speed to
his advantage! Uh-huh!
He's out of there!
And Cocculeen's car is
safely on the ground!
You did it!
The weaker car loses in a collision.
Giving up power to ram me will
prove to be a costly mistake.
Instead of gloating,
you should have paid more
attention to my plan to stay
behind and knock you off
course with a spin attack.
So you say though the same
could also be said of you?
Losing power was not an accident.
You're so self-righteous in your hubris.
You didn't realize I planned for
you to knock my car off course
Everything rests on this
Look closely.
Do you see where my car is headed?
He landed on the other side,
farther ahead at that! Impossible!
Yes, ordinarily.
Even at one's top speed,
a move like the one I just did
usually would result in a crash.
You wouldn't make it by
jumping over the curves.
But it's another story completely
if you're catapulted over them.
All I needed was your help.
From the moment we left the tunnel,
my plan was to get you to hit
me by sacrificing my power.
That said, I think it's time we
continued our race, don't you?
Don't let this guy get to
you, Kakyoin! Stay focused!
Kakyoin!
There, now his soul belongs to me.
The poor fool admitted defeat.
He finally realized that it was
pointless to continue racing.
Still, I must say,
you, Kakyoin, are the first opponent
to ever make me perspire like this.
Given its source material,
this doll will make a most exquisite
addition to my growing collection.
He was the very first opponent
to muster up the courage to
conquer his fears and resist cracking
under such colossal pressure.
I will treasure his good company always.
Careful,
it would be in the best interest of all
involved for you to keep
your emotions in check.
Harming me is out of the question.
You see, dying is something I simply
can't do if you want your friend back.
Slipping on a banana
peel and hitting my head.
choking on gum,
or even suffering a heart attack from
the shock of popping a bag of popcorn.
If any of those things sent me to
heaven, Kakyoin's soul would go too.
The end of the night, and the
dark in the end of the night,
the moon has been sent to
the moonlight in the sea.
I don't know if it's
the word of the night.
I'd never see the number of night.
I'm still in my own way,
and I'm still in my own way.
When I get to the end of the night,
I'm running back in the battle,
The end
of
the world,
Keine Ahitzabe,
Hora, What the? Hey!
Hey, Jotaro, wait! What's this?
Hey, Jotaro!
Why the hell are you sitting down?
We should be kicking Geppetto's ass!
I'll play him next!
Old man, have you ever actually
played any of these games?
If not, the odds wouldn't
be in your favor.
Stay out of it, old man.
This isn't your average
game of gin rummy after all.
We're playing baseball.
That's the game I choose
to settle this once
and for all as collateral
I'll bet my soul!
All right then I would like to bet Kakyoin
soul my stand Atum has released your arm
you may thank me at your leisure now that
Kakyoin soul is in my collection there's
no longer reason for me to keep your arm
in my stands' clutches and suffice it
to say i'd be at a bit of a disadvantage
if i faced you with my stand one handed!
I'm all aware of your star platinum's
incredible speed and precision!
Really out of all the games
you could have chosen to play
it's unfortunate for you that
we're playing my specialty!
Darby!
Just you wait the moment Jotaro
wipes the floor with you I'll
throttle the life out of your
pompous ass and that is a promise!
Oh that's
a baseball!
Doesn't look like he's
tempered with this game either!
You're good to go!
Before we begin you'll
need to pick your team!
Jaguars
Jaguars!
Yes, I see.
You've decided to go with a team
that has a strong offense, eh?
And two with a batting average over 400.
If that's how you're going to play
it, I'll choose the Red Dragons.
Red Dragons!
Offense or defense?
Go on, take your pick.
Offense.
In that case, the Jaguars will bat first.
Next, you can begin designing your own
players by drawing their faces on the screen.
This handsome devil is Star Platinum.
Now that we've gotten the
preparations out of the way...
Playball!
Jaguars versus Red Dragons!
I've chosen number 15 as my pitcher.
January 5th is my birthday, you know.
Now, here we go.
The pitcher is winding up!
The first pitch!
What?
Strike one!
Uh, hey, I don't get it! What's wrong?
That was a pretty amateur move back there.
It's great that you swung the bat and all,
but it was before he even threw the ball!
Hey, what's this all about?
There's no need for you to
practice your swing, is there?
Hang on!
Jotaro, is this the very first
time you've ever played this?
In fact, have you ever played
a video game in your life?
You answer me right now, Jotaro!
Relax.
I already know how to play baseball.
I'll figure out the game controls as I go.
What are you saying?
In case you haven't noticed,
your timing is totally off!
Your swings are pathetic!
Don't lie, this is your
first time playing, isn't it?
Strike two!
And now you're actually swinging the bat
after the catcher has caught the ball!
You don't know what you're doing!
Dammit, Jotaro, I was right!
You don't know a video game
from a hole in the ground!
Strike! Better out!
Jotaro, it's time to get serious!
Stop trying to act cool
and use your blasted head!
You bet your soul on this game,
so if you think you can back
out due to lack of experience,
think again!
Good grief.
This is the worst pep
talk I've ever heard.
You should be more encouraging.
Try something like, it's only the first
inning, you can still make a comeback.
What the hell's going
through that head of yours?
You can't possibly rely solely on Star
Platinum's reflexes to win this game,
can you?
Think about it!
You don't know the first
thing about video games!
How are you supposed to beat him?
What's your plan, Jotaro?
Answer me, damn it!
Do you have a way to
beat this weirdo or not?
Jotaro?
Listen,
if your strategy is to trick me
by pretending to be an amateur,
let me inform you that
it isn't going to work.
I'd never be foolish enough
to let my guard down.
Even if you were a helpless
child, it wouldn't happen.
A soul is at stake.
Old man.
Since you wanted to know,
I don't have a plan.
However, if I did have one,
the only thing it would involve would be
knocking the nose straight off the face?
of this condescending, overinflated douchebag
of a prick taking up space beside me.
All I care about is getting
Kakyoin's soul back.
I'll do whatever it takes.
You talk a big game,
but it's still the top of the
first inning and you have won out.
The match is far from over.
And since you haven't played before?
You should know that if you fall
more than 11 points behind you lose!
Second batter number three?
Strike.
Damn, he's getting even worse that time.
He swung the bat over 40
centimeters above the ball.
How's he so bad?
Strike two what it wasn't even close
Strike three! You're out!
It's all over.
Jotaro's no match for someone like Darby.
This massacre is like being forced
to watch a group of high school
baseball champs go head-to-head
with kids from the knitting club.
It's pathetic!
Strike one! Strike two!
So, it wasn't a bluff.
He really is a beginner.
This is too easy.
In the same way a judo pro
can gauge his opponent's
skill simply by looking at
the way he wears his gi,
I can read him like a book.
And chapter one is called
Jotaro, the Video Game Novice.
All the same, I refuse
to let my guard down.
I'm aware of the weaknesses
of every batter in this game.
Next will be a low pitch to the outside.
I'll throw my best pitch, the
four-seam fastball, and strike him out.
It's the first inning.
Two outs, two strikes, and no fouls.
Here comes my next pitch.
Go right ahead.
I've pretty much gotten the hang
of batting with the controller.
Wait, what did he just say?
I must have heard him wrong.
What does he mean, got the hang of it?
Surely he couldn't have...
What is he talking about?
What does he mean?
What?!
Jotaro!
All right, I'm really starting to
enjoy this game. What in the...
It can't be! It's going!
The ball is still going!
It just doesn't make sense.
What did he mean by, got the hang of it?
Got the hang of it?
Ah!
He...
He did it!
I don't know how, but he did it!
Hey, run!
Home Run!
It's a home run!
Jotaro! Damn you!
Jotaro!
Did I really hear you
correctly? Say something.
It sounded like you've pretty
much gotten the hang of batting.
I don't feel like repeating myself.
He was a beginner when we
started this game. And yet,
he's claiming to have learned proper
swinging technique in only eight pitches.
Jotaro Code has all the speed
and dexterity of Star Platinum.
Now I know why Master Dio finds him to
be problematic and why my brother lost.
Interesting.
I couldn't have asked for
a more fitting opponent.
But as naturally gifted as you may be,
you made a critical mistake by revealing
your talents so early in the game.
A mistake that will cost you dearly.
Let's resume the game, Jotaro.
Yes, he did it!
That's my boy!
Another home run right out of the park!
Talk about a comeback!
Four runs in the first inning!
Looks like you've got this
game in the bag, Jotaro!
Keep it up, and we'll be
out of here in no time!
Hey, Darby, you'll just ignore me, but
I'll say it anyway because I'm a nice guy.
I'm giving you an out.
All you have to do is return Kakyoin's soul
and take us to Dio of your own volition.
If you cooperate, no harm will befall you!
Huh?
For all his faults, my
brother was a master gambler.
He made conning people into an art form.
You'd think his younger brother
would be perfect to practice on.
But you'd be wrong.
He never asked me to
play one game of poker.
No, I was never asked to play any
games of the gambling persuasion.
Any guesses why?
When I was 15,
I caught my brother putting his
oh-so-predictable moves on my girlfriend.
He was 10 years older, but
I beat him to a bloody pulp.
I broke his ribs and proceeded
to kick him until he spat blood.
The last thing my brother said
to me was how sorry he was.
Any idea why?
Would you please cut to the chase already?
Even as kids,
my brother had the good sense to realize
that he'd never have
what it took to beat me.
The reason for that is about
to become abundantly clear.
At this moment, you have a false sense of
confidence due to the home run you hit.
But deep down, you feel a sense of
unease, not unlike what my brother felt.
My prowess is beginning
to worry you, isn't it?
Right now, you're coming to a daunting
conclusion about the game's outcome,
aren't you, Jotaro?
What the hell are you talking about?
Changing pictures number 15
is out and number 77 is in.
77 is a power pitcher with a max pitch
speed of 165 kilometers per hour.
Also I'll tell you the pitch
I'll throw number 77 will
throw a forkball and he'll
throw it right down the middle.
What the hell why would he
declare what he's Throwing
a fork ball is about to
come barreling down center,
but will you believe me or not?
Jotaro he's just spouting
nonsense to shake your confidence
do yourself a favor and
ignore everything he says.
Throw it Darby!
Will you believe or will you doubt?
I knew it.
It's a fastball, and
it's coming right at you.
Let's see is the ball
going to change direction?
The suspense is driving me crazy!
You swung!
You bought his act and
bet on the forkball!
It's still going!
It actually is a fastball!
Oh great, he hit the bottom of the ball!
Out!
First inning, three outs change!
Idiot, how could you?
Leave it to a rookie
for something like that!
I can't believe you swung for a forkball!
Hmph.
No.
He had already seen through me and knew
I would swing expecting a forkball.
So we switched it up to a fastball.
But he has a point, though.
Something's been gnawing at me ever
since we stepped foot in this mansion.
I'm not sure how.
But he knew Star Platinum would throw
a right punch in our earlier skirmish.
What?
Impossible!
Are you trying to tell me
that he can read your mind?
No offense, Jotaro, but that's crazy talk.
Oh, would you look at that.
It's my turn at bat.
This is going to be a home run.
Keep your eye on the birdie, as I'll be
hitting it into the left field bleachers.
Old man, are you absolutely sure?
The game and console
haven't been tampered with.
Yeah, I'm positive it's
clean and that's not all.
I haven't seen him make a
single funny move either.
Then a secret weapon has
to be that stand of his.
His stand doesn't just take souls
it must have some other ability.
This will be my target.
Now I'll get to the bottom of this.
Has he lost his mind?
He's going to try to hit the better on
purpose and where might you be aiming?
Now Jotaro, an inside pitch
will you throw it high or low?
Perhaps or maybe you're planning
some kind of underhanded trick?
Well.
What the people back with
Jotaro through the ball?
He predicted it.
He knew exactly what
would happen. But how?
There's no way he could have seen that
pitch coming unless he read Jotaro's mind.
Home run!
That's one run.
Damn this bastard.
We faced all kinds of
opponents on this journey,
but never one who could read our minds.
If you really can read minds, then it
doesn't matter how clever we think we are.
We won't stand a
snowball's chance in hell!
Jotaro, what are you going to do?
Why that?
Damn, the punk's declaring
another home run!
Let's see.
An outside pitch?
Or maybe you're going to aim low, or
something in the vein of a fastball.
Home run!
Four to two.
Damn!
A person's body language and
the surrounding environment go
a long way toward helping
predict an opponent's next move.
But there's no way to do
it perfectly and yet his
stand predicts Jotaro's pitch
with 100 % accuracy and!
Technically, he's not cheating?
Another home run!
It's 4-3!
How are we supposed to stop
him from reading our minds?
How?
At this rate, I'll be in the
lead in no time. Now what's next?
An inside pitch, a fastball, a
high pitch, or maybe a curveball?
What's up your sleeve?
Huh?
Your hat.
You idiot.
Do you honestly take me for a cheat
like my ne 'er-do-well brother?
Jotaro, you've got it wrong.
Hiding your face is useless.
I don't know what he's doing,
but he's not watching the reflection
of the screen in your eyes.
I get that it's hard not to go there now,
but there's no way he can see what you're
pressing or what pitch you're choosing.
Trust me, I've been watching
him the entire time.
That's not what's been going on here.
I only took off my hat
because I'm sweating.
No other reason.
Could you throw your next
pitch sometime this year?
But I'm not going to be sweating anymore.
I'll tell you my next pitch.
I'm throwing a high outside fastball.
You're joking! Totoro!
Do you hear what you're saying right now?
Of course I do.
Finally starting to lose
your hearing, old man.
Obviously, I just told him my next pitch.
A high outside fastball.
That's how I'm gonna win.
Huh? Jotaro?
Will you believe me?
Or will you doubt me?
Hmph.
You're not too bright, are you?
Do you hear what you're saying right now?
Obviously, I just told him my next pitch.
What the hell?
He's telling the truth!
Yes.
You tampered with the console!
No!
It must have something to
do with that hat of yours!
This is just a dance of deception
where the loser cries first.